{
  "heading": "Contraction",
  "topics": [
    {
      "heading": "Contraction",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionNo": 1,
          "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct contraction:<br> We ____ going to the zoo today.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "aren’t" },
            { "text": "is'nt" },
            { "text": "doesn’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 2,
          "question": "Which is the contraction for \"He will\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "He’ll" },
            { "text": "He’s" },
            { "text": "He do’nt" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 3,
          "question": "Which is the contraction for \"She will\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "She’s" },
            { "text": "She’ll" },
            { "text": "She do’nt" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 4,
          "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct contraction:<br> I ____ believe in magic.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "don't" },
            { "text": "isn't" },
            { "text": "do’nt" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 5,
          "question": "Which is the contraction for \"They are\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "They are’t" },
            { "text": "They’nt" },
            { "text": "They’re" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 6,
          "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct contraction:<br> I ____ believe this is the right answer.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "don't" },
            { "text": "doesn't" },
            { "text": "isn’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 7,
          "question": "What is the contraction for \"I am\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "Im" },
            { "text": "I’nt" },
            { "text": "I’m" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 8,
          "question": "Which is the contraction for \"are not\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "ar’ent" },
            { "text": "aren’t" },
            { "text": "are’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 9,
          "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct contraction:<br> They ____ coming to the party tomorrow.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "doesn’t" },
            { "text": "isn't" },
            { "text": "aren't" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 10,
          "question": "What is the contraction for \"I have\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "I’ve" },
            { "text": "I am" },
            { "text": "I have’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 11,
          "question": "Which is the contraction for \"You have\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "You are" },
            { "text": "You’ve" },
            { "text": "You have’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 12,
          "question": "Choose the correct contraction for the sentence:<br> ___ going to the park later.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "He’s" },
            { "text": "He is" },
            { "text": "She is" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 13,
          "question": "Fill in the blank with the correct contraction:<br> She said ___ coming to the party.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "It’s" },
            { "text": "She’s" },
            { "text": "He’s" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 14,
          "question": "Choose the contraction that matches the sentence:<br> ___ my best friend in the whole world!",
          "options": [
            { "text": "You’re" },
            { "text": "Your" },
            { "text": "We’re" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 15,
          "question": "Complete the sentence with the right contraction:<br> ___ going to the zoo tomorrow.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "Aren’t" },
            { "text": "We’re" },
            { "text": "Weren’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 16,
          "question": "Choose the correct contraction for “Has not”.",
          "options": [
            { "text": "Haven’t" },
            { "text": "Has’nt" },
            { "text": "Hasn’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 17,
          "question": "Which contraction means \"Does not\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "Doesn’t" },
            { "text": "Isn’t" },
            { "text": "Aren’t" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 18,
          "question": "Which contraction means \"She is\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "She’s" },
            { "text": "We’re" },
            { "text": "It’s" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 19,
          "question": "Which contraction means \"We are\"?",
          "options": [
            { "text": "Aren’t" },
            { "text": "We’re" },
            { "text": "He’s" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "questionNo": 20,
          "question": "Choose the contraction for \"It is.\"",
          "options": [
            { "text": "It’s" },
            { "text": "I’ts" },
            { "text": "Its" }
          ],
          "answer": 0
        }
      ]
      
      
    }
  ]
}
